Hello.
こんにちは
What are you doing now?
今って何されてる方ですか?
I'm a student.
学生です
You're a student.
学生なんですね
Are you a university student?
大学生ですか?
yes.
はい
I see.
なるほど
What do you think?
どうですか?
Do you enjoy your student life?
学生生活楽しいですか?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Did you get a boyfriend?
彼氏とかできました?
I haven't been able to do it.
できてないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
How long have you not had a boyfriend?
どれぐらい今、彼氏いないですか?
He's not there anymore.
もういないですね
I don't even remember.
覚えてないぐらい
There aren't as many as I can remember.
覚えてないぐらいいないです
But don't you meet many people?
でも 出会いたくさんないですか?
It's a student.
学生さんだと
Not really.
そうでもないです
Do you not go to many clubs?
あんまりサークルとかも行かないですか?
By the way, you said you don't have a boyfriend.
ちなみに彼氏さんはいないって言ってましたけど、
Do you have someone with whom you do such naughty things?
そういったエッチなことする相手とかっています?
Yes, that's not the case either.
はい、それもいないです
Have you ever done that with anyone other than your boyfriend?
彼氏以外はそういうことをしたことないですか?
No.
ないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
When was the last time you did something like that?
最後にそういうのしたのはいつですか?
I don't even remember.
覚えてないぐらい
I don't remember.
覚えてないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
I feel like I'm being reminded,
思い出してもらう感じになっちゃうんですけど、
Do you have a favorite body?
好きな体とかってあります?
Is it a bag?
バッグですかね
Why is that?
それはなんで?
why?
なんで?
Will it hit the back?
奥に当たるかな?
I guess you like the interior.
奥好きなんですね
I like it.
好きです
What do you do alone?
一人でおなにとかってします?
yes.
はい
Do you use toys that hit the back?
奥に当たるおもちゃとか使ったりするんですか?
sometimes.
たまに
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうなんですね
By the way, how long do you use it?
ちなみにどれくらいの長さを使っていますか?
Could you please show me your hand for a moment?
今ちょっと手で表してもらっていいですか?
That's about it.
これくらい
That's about the length.
長さ、それくらい
I think that's probably it.
多分これくらいだと思います
Do you feel like you can use it by inserting the length?
長さのを入れて使うって感じですか?
That's right.
そうなんですね
By the way, when was the last time you were alone?
ちなみに、最後に一人でしたのはいつですか?
Show me, I don't remember.
見せだろ、覚えてないです
I don't remember that either.
それも覚えてないです
Maybe just recently?
多分つい最近くらいかな?
recently?
最近?
After all, should you do it at night?
やっぱりやるときは夜ですか?
Or do you just do it without really caring?
それともあんまり関係なくやってます?
It's night, it's night.
夜ですね、夜ですね
How long is the cycle?
どれくらいの周期とかあります?
cycle?
周期?
Nothing in particular.
特にないです
What if you think of it?
思い立ったら?
If you think about it, yes.
思い立ったら、そうですね
That's right.
そうなんですね
Then.
そしたらですね
Wait a minute, clothes.
ちょっとじゃあ、服
Cute clothes.
可愛らしい服
Shall I take it off for once?
一回脱いちゃいましょうか
Can I have you stand there in your underwear for once?
一回下着姿で、その場に立ってみてもらっていいですか?
yes.
はい
Then, shall I take off my underwear?
そしたら、下着も脱いちゃいましょうか
yes.
はい
Can you open your legs?
足開けますか?
On the spot.
その場で
So, let's open that one too.
で、あそこも開いちゃいましょうか
yes.
はい
Can I have you spin around in there?
その場でぐるっと回ってもらっていいですか?
Please show me your butt too.
お尻も見せてください
Can you open your butt yourself?
お尻も自分で開けますか?
yes.
はい
Then, let's sit on the sofa.
そ したら、ソファーに座っちゃいましょう
Please make it into an M shape.
M字になってもらって
Can I have a closer look at it again?
またよく見せてもらっていいですか?
Please come a little closer to the sofa.
もうちょっと、ソファーに手前に来てもらって
Shall I try it myself?
自分でじってみようか
Then, open it well and open it firmly?
そ したら、 よく開いて、しっかりと開ける?
yes.
はい
Shall I try putting this in?
これ、入れてみようか
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
It's going to be four places.
ちょっと四つの場になっちゃう
Can I put it in myself?
自分で入れる?
yes.
はい
Will you open it for me?
開いてあげる?
Can you move it yourself?
自分で動かせる?
yes.
はい
Shall I turn to face you?
顔向きになっちゃおうか
Try to put your feet in, show me well.
足入れしようと、よく見せて
Show me, show me.
見せて見せて
After looking at it for a while, I got horny too.
ちょっと見てたら、やっぱさ、 俺もムラムラしちゃったからさ
This is also a bit,
これもちょっとさ、
Eat it.
食べ て
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Then, continuing from before, I would like you to open your legs again.
そ したら、さっきの続き、 ちょっと足また開いてもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
Another toy that's a little different from before.
ちょっと さっきとは違うおもちゃまた
A slightly different toy than before.
さっきとは違うおもちゃでちょっと
Okay.
よし
Shall I lie down?
横になっちゃおうか
Lie down now.
横になって、今
Is it okay to just use my hands?
手だけで大丈夫かな?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Lie down.
横 にな って
Open your legs.
足開いて
open?
開ける?
Keep your legs wide open.
足しっかりと開いて
often
よ く
show me.
見 せて
My legs really came out.
めっちゃ足を出てきちゃった
I'm chewing a lot.
めちゃくちゃ噛んでる
I was excited when I saw it.
見てたら、興奮してるけど
He has great legs.
足の偉いって
Are you licking it?
舐めてる?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Should I sleep?
寝ておくか
Sleep on top.
上に寝て
Sleep in the back.
後ろに寝て
Can you move?
動ける?
Can you move up?
上に動ける?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Shall we do it from behind?
後ろからしようか
over there.
あそこ
あ そこ
Can you push it up?
押し上げれる?
thank you.
ありがとう
Lie down.
横になって
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Want to try it yourself?
自分でやってみる?